Contact

8082068480 (Mobile) rohitprajapati0307@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/rohit-k-prajapati-b47b3a130 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

WordPress

HTML

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Languages

Marathi

Hindi

English

Rohit K. Prajapati

Frontend Developer | Web Developer | Wordpress Developer | Mumbai

Summary

My name is Rohit K. Prajapati, a front end WordPress Developer with more than 3 years of experience. I have held developer position in 2 companies mainly working on WordPress, HTML, CSS and Javascript.

When I was with Beyondt company I worked on 10+ WordPress websites out of which 3+ are woocommerce based websites.

I worked on many websites when Marqetrix Web Solutions.

All WordPress, HTML, CSS and JavaScript based websites used to be here.

I have 6+ HTML, CSS and Javascript based websites.

I am looking for a challenging job where I can hone my skills, develop my creativity and put my maximum effort on the assigned work and take an active part in the growth of the company.

Experience

Della Leaders
Frontend Web Developer | WordPress Developer
2021 - Present (1 year)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Beyondt

Web Developer
July 2018 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Mumbai Area, India

I was here as web designer and wordpress developer. What kind of website does the customer want, I take all the information related to it, then what kind of business I want to do on the website, I make it from that level. Theme and plugin research and implementation the way the customer wants the website. And I had a lot of responsibility, like

- Maintaining all website.
- All website hosting and maintenance.
- All domain hosting email maintenance.

- Fixed all website bugs, etc.

Marqetrix Web Solutions Wordpress Developer June 2020 - May 2021 (1 year)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

I was here as web designer and wordpress developer. I used to get this new task every day and used to resolve it. Create new website, customized page, theme and plugin customizer.

And I had a lot of responsibility, like

- Maintenance of all website.
- All website hosting and maintenance.
- All domain hosting email maintenance.
- Fixed all website bugs, etc.

grofers

MIS Executive Manager August 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 2 months) Chandivali Mumbai Maharashtra, India

I was here in the MIS Executive Manager Position. On this, I used to do all the checking every day how many orders came and how many orders went. Which delivery boy is the on which route? How much the order was received by the

customer, how much was not received, what was missing, how much was the damaged product status. To maintain on the live sheet and email end of the slot updated. And a lot of responsibility was on me.

NETSPIDER INFOTECH INDIA LIMITED. (NIIL)

2 years 5 months

Team Leader | Data Operations Manager | Software Developer December 2015 - November 2016 (1 year)

Sakinaka Mumbai Maharashtra, India

Team Leader | Data Operations Manager January 2015 - November 2015 (11 months)

Sakinaka Mumbai Maharashtra, India

Data Operator

July 2014 - June 2015 (1 year)

Sakinaka Mumbai Maharashtra, India

Education

University of Mumbai
Bachelor of Science (BSc), Computer Science · (2013 - 2016)

Shriniwas Bagarka Junior College
J B Nagar, Mumbai-400059.
Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC), Computer and Information Sciences,
General · (July 2010 - May 2012)

Shivam Vidya Mandir High School And Junior College, Mumbai Secondary School Certificate (SSC), General Studies · (May 2010)